Guide to the William S. Downing papers, 1922-2006.
Downing, William S. papers,
- Series II. Project Records
  - J.N. Adam -Preliminary Info, Program Info, Site Photos, 1986 (Box 90)
  - J.N. Adam -Preliminary Info, Program Info, Site Photos, 1986 (Box 91)
  - Monarch Machine Tool Co. Edlund - Correspondence, Supervision Records, Inspection Records, Payment certificates, Change Orders, Daily Diary, Shop Dwgs - Arch, Cortland, New York, 1966 (Box 91)
  - Monarch Machine Tool Co. Edlund - Correspondence, Supervision Records, Inspection Records, Payment certificates, Change Orders, Daily Diary, Shop Dwgs - Arch, Cortland, New York, 1966 (Box 92)
  - Monarch Machine Tool Co. Edlund - Correspondence, Supervision Records, Inspection Records, Payment certificates, Change Orders, Daily Diary, Shop Dwgs - Arch, Cortland, New York, 1966 (Box 93)
  - Moog 11A, 1975 (Box 93)
    Project # 75-477
  - Moog 11A, 1975 (Box 94)
  - Tuning Fork Building - General, 1968 (Box 94)
    Project # 68-429
  - Divi Divi, 1968 (Box 95)
  - Divi Divi, 1969 (Box 95)
  - Divi Divi, 1973 (Box 95)
  - Tamarijn Hotel, 1974 (Box 95)
    Project # 74-464
  - Seneca Lake State Park (Box 95)
  - FLSPC Fair Haven Beach, Fair Haven, New York, 1965 (Box 95)
  - Watkins Glen State Park Swimming Pool & Boathouse, Watkins Glen, New York (Box 96)
  - Old Courthouse (Tompkins County Courthouse) - Preservation and Remodel, Ithaca, New York, 1973 (Box 96)
    Project # 73-460
  - Old Courthouse (Tompkins County Courthouse) - Preservation and Remodel, Ithaca, New York, 1973 (Box 97)
  - Ramada Towers and Remodel, Ithaca, New York, 1982 (Box 97)
    Project # 82-552
  - Ramada Towers and Remodel, Ithaca, New York, 1982 (Box 97)
    Project # 82-554
  - Ramada Towers and Remodel, Ithaca, New York, 1982 (Box 98)
  - Ramada Towers and Remodel, Ithaca, New York, 1982 (Box 98)
  - Ramada Towers and Remodel, Ithaca, New York, 1982 (Box 99)
  - Ramada Towers and Remodel, Ithaca, New York, 1982 (Box 99)
  - Skaneateles Lake Report, 1967 (Box 99)
  - Election Survey - Post Election Analysis, 1963 (Box 99)
  - Foreign Policy (Box 99)
  - Foreign Policy Speech (Box 99)
  - Goldwater, 1964 (Box 99)
  - Lindsey, 1965 (Box 99)
  - Lo Pinto, 1964 (Box 99)
  - Politics, 1972 (Box 99)
  - Ithaca Water System, 1972 (Box 99)
  - City Water and Sewers, 1963 (Box 99)
  - BPW Water (Box 99)
  - Thaler (Box 99)
  - General (Box 99)
  - YMCA - Proposed Building, Ithaca, New York, 1964 (Box 99)
  - Route 96 (Box 99)
  - Summer Buying (Box 99)
  - Spring/Summer Buying (Box 99)
  - Technical Data (Box 99)
  - Gallery Fall Purchases (Box 99)
  - Sharon Davis (Box 99)
  - Gallery - Employees (Box 99)
  - Gallery Credit Rating (Box 99)
  - Gallery 1968, 1968 (Box 99)
  - Gallery Boutique General (Box 99)
  - Republican Party, Ithaca, New York, 1965 (Box 99)
  - Secretary Position, 1970 (Box 99)
  - Investments (Box 99)
  - Phyllis Downing Correspondence (Box 99)
  - Fran Taylor Correspondence (Box 99)
  - Dorris Downing Correspondence (Box 99)
  - Bill Correspondence (Box 99)
  - Betty Gail Downing Correspondence (Box 99)
  - Downing Residence (Box 99)
  - Robert Downing Correspondence (Box 99)
  - Betsy Correspondence (Box 99)
  - June Correspondence (Box 99)
  - Correspondence 1956 etc., 1956 (Box 99)
  - Jeanne (Box 99)
  - Marshall H. Earl (Box 99)
  - 2320 Crestmont Ave. (Box 100)
  - Mr. & Mrs. William S. Downing (Box 100)
  - B.G. - N.Y.U. (Box 100)
  - Elaine T. Downing (Box 100)
  - Elmhurst (Box 100)
  - Photographs of Children (Box 100)
  - B.G. (Box 100)
  - Jeanne (Box 100)
  - WSD III (Box 100)
  - Dutch Village, 1982 (Box 100)
    Project # 82-547
  - Monarch, 1984 (Box 100)
    Project # 84-573
  - I.C. .CSB Construction Meeting Minutes, 1983 (Box 100)
  - Old Library on Church Street, 1984 (Box 100)
  - Adirondack Kitchen, 1983 (Box 100)
    Project # 83-564
  - West End - Lake Side, 1982 (Box 100)
  - Brown Cottage, 1981 (Box 100)
  - Strand Theatre, Ithaca, New York, 1980 (Box 100)
  - TCTC (Tompkins County Trust Company) - Addition, 1982 (Box 100)
  - College Avenue, 1981 (Box 100)
    Project # 81-537
  - Tamarijn Dining, 1981 (Box 100)
    Project # 81-530
  - Ithaca Center Bar, Ithaca, New York, 1981 (Box 100)
    Project # 81-534
  - Cortland Courthouse, Cortland, New York, 1981 (Box 100)
    Project # 81-538
  - Aruba Façade Study, 1981 (Box 100)
    Project # 81-541
  - Munchmeyer, 1982 (Box 100)
  - Central Ave. Redevelopment, 1981 (Box 100)
    Project # 81-527
  - Biggs Center, 1980 (Box 100)
    Project # 80-525
  - Trumansburg Boiler, Trumansburg, New York, 1981 (Box 100)
    Project # 81-535
  - Trumansburg Shop, Trumansburg, New York, 1981 (Box 100)
    Project # 81-542
  - Trumansburg Reroof, Trumansburg, New York, 1981 (Box 100)
  - Divi Divi DOS, 1982 (Box 100)
    Project # 82-556
  - Divi Divi, 1981 (Box 100)
    Project # 81-531
  - Divi Divi, 1981 (Box 100)
    Project # 81-545
  - Tamarijn Bunker Bar, 1982 (Box 100)
    Project # 82-546
  - Monarch, 1979 (Box 100)
  - Meadow House, 1984 (Box 100)
    Project # 84-687
  - Phillippine Factory MOOG, 1984 (Box 100)
    Project # 84-580
  - Tiara Beach Hotel, 1983 (Box 100)
    Project # 83-559
  - Schoolhouse Manor, 1980 (Box 100)
  - Ramada Rear Entry, Ithaca, New York, 1983 (Box 100)
    Project # 83-560
  - Ramada Tower Billings, Ithaca, New York, 1982 (Box 100)
  - Ramada Inn Remodeling, Ithaca, New York, 1982 (Box 100)
  - Natural Lean Pork Inc., 1984 (Box 100)
    Project # 84-577
  - Ruteledge Residence, 1983 (Box 100)
    Project # 83-567
  - Wong Apt. Building, 1982 (Box 100)
    Project # 82-548
  - American Home Funding inc., 1984 (Box 100)
    Project # 84-571
  - Cornell University - Snee Hall, Ithaca, New York, 1984 (Box 100)
    Project # 84-583
  - Cornell University - Ag Quad Urban Design Study, Ithaca, New York, 1984 (Box 100)
    Project # 84-579
  - Cornell University - Hoy Field Landscape/Parking Study, Ithaca, New York, 1984 (Box 100)
    Project # 84-578
  - Cornell University - Hoy Field Planning & Parking Structure Study, Ithaca, New York, 1984 (Box 100)
  - Cornell University - Parking/Sports Complex, Ithaca, New York, 1984 (Box 100)
    Project # 84-570
  - Tobin Fieldhouse, Cornell University, Ithaca, New York, 1984 (Box 100)
    Project # 84-575
  - Tobin Fieldhouse Revision, Cornell University, Ithaca, New York, 1984 (Box 100)
    Project # 84-858
  - Cornell University Fraternity/Sorority, Ithaca, New York, 1984 (Box 100)
    Project # 84-572
  - Alfred U.B. (Box 100)
  - Mr. Moog's Office (Box 100)
  - Ithaca Gun Company, Ithaca, New York (Box 100)
  - Monarch Tool & Machine Company, Edlund Division, Cortland, New York (Box 100)
  - Period Storefronts - Photographs (Box 101)
  - Tompkins County Houses - Photographs (Box 101)
  - Danby Elementary School (Box 101)
  - Danby School Transmittals - Revised Plans, 1961 (Box 101)
  - Finger Lakes State Park Commission - Administration Building (Box 101)
  - Dryden Church Bids, Dryden, New York, 1965 (Box 101)
    Project # 315
  - Marathon Central School, Marathon, New York (Box 101)
    Project # 349
  - Egbert, P.T. Garage (Box 101)
    Project # 283
  - Tioga Schools Miscellaneous (Box 101)
  - Dr. Peter Auer Residence (Box 101)
    Project # 407
  - J.D. Hartman, 1959 (Box 101)
  - Alpha Epsilon Phi, Ithaca, New York, 1954 (Box 101)
  - Delta Gamma Sorority, 1961 (Box 101)
  - Frank G. Finch, 1959 (Box 101)
  - Holcomb Data (Box 101)
  - Cayuga Lodge, 1961 (Box 101)
  - Joseph Eberle, 1955 (Box 101)
  - Francis Bartow (Box 101)
  - F.H. Hill, 1963 (Box 101)
  - First Baptist Church (Box 101)
  - Taughannock Falls State Park, 1961 (Box 101)
  - Hyde Hall, 1965 (Box 101)
- Series III. Specifications
  - C of C (Chamber of Commerce) Specs, 1980 (Box 7)
  - Bathhouse Complex, Seneca Lake State Park, near Geneva, New York, 1965 (Box 19)
    Project # 65-3959
  - Office Building, Shephard Niles Crane & Hoist Co., Montour Falls, New York, 1967 (Box 19)
    Project # 67-409
  - Region 2 Headquarters, New York S Conservation Dept., Little Valley, New York, 1968 (Box 19)
  - Old Courthouse, Tompkins County, Ithaca, New York, 1973 (Box 19)
  - Building 11A Moog Inc., East Aurora, New York, 1975 (Box 19)
  - Buildings 4 & 6 Moog Inc., East Aurora, New York, 1975 (Box 19)
    Project # 75-478
  - Buildings 4 & 6 Moog Inc., East Aurora, New York, 1975 (Box 19)
    Project # 75-479
  - Tompkins County Trust Co. Drive In Facitlity, Ithaca, New York, 1976 (Box 19)
  - Maintenance Shop B, State Armory, Staten Island, New York, 1976 (Box 19)
    Project # M0058
  - Tompkins County Trust Co. Building, Ithaca, New York, 1977 (Box 19)
    Project # 77-34
  - Plant 4 Moog Inc., East Aurora, New York, 1978 (Box 19)
  - Moog Inc. Building 11B, East Aurora, New York, 1978 (Box 20)
    Project # 78-499
  - St. John's Episcopal Church Renovation, Ithaca, New York, 1978 (Box 20)
  - Monarch/Cortland Additions - Material Handling, Cortland, New York, 1979 (Box 20)
  - Monarch Reroofing, Cortland, New York, 1979 (Box 20)
    Project # 79-515
  - Monarch Machine Tool Co. Pre-purchase Specs, 1979 (Box 20)
  - Plant 11C, Moog Inc., East Aurora, New York, 1980 (Box 20)
    Project # 80-519
  - Strand Theatre Renovations, Ithaca, New York, 1980 (Box 20)
  - Boiler Replacement, Trumansburg Central School District #1, Trumansburg, New York, 1981 (Box 20)
  - Dutch Village, Aruba, Netherlands, Antillies, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Ramada Tower, Ithaca, New York, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Tiara Beach Hotel, Cayman Brac, Cayman Island, B.W.I., 1983 (Box 20)
  - Renovations of Tompkins County Public Library, Ithaca, New York, 1983 (Box 20)
    Project # 83-563
  - Rutledge Residence, Interlaken, New York, 1983 (Box 20)
  - La Tourelle, Ithaca, New York, 1983 (Box 20)
    Project # 83-568
  - Tobin Field House, Cornell University, 1984 (Box 20)
  - Delavan Residence, Seneca Falls, New York, 1984 (Box 20)
  - Ithaca Youth Bureau, Ithaca, New York, 1984 (Box 20)
    Project # 84-584
  - Black Oak Lane, Ithaca, New York, 1985 (Box 21)
    Project # 85-592
  - Massanutten Village, Administration Buildings, Harrisonburg, VA, 1985 (Box 21)
  - Strand Theatre Roof Renovation, Ithaca, New York, 1986 (Box 21)
    Project # 86-602
  - New Day Treatment Facility, Perrysburg, New York, 1986 (Box 21)
    Project # 86-608
  - Ciaschi Building, Ithaca, New York, 1987 (Box 21)
  - Ithaca Childcare Center, Ithaca, New York, 1987 (Box 21)
    Project # 87-616
  - Armory, Dryden, New York, 1987 (Box 21)
    Project # MO-597
  - Corcoran/Herson/Weaver Residence, Ithaca, New York, 1988 (Box 21)
    Project # 88-627
  - Sears Residence, Spencer, New York, 1988 (Box 21)
    Project # 88-628
  - Dyckman Residence, 1988 (Box 21)
    Project # 88-629
  - Tompkins County Chamber of Commerce, Ithaca, New York, 1988 (Box 22)
  - Tompkins County Old Courthouse Handicap Ramp, Ithaca, New York, 1988 (Box 22)
    Project # 88-639
  - St. John's Episcopal Church, Ithaca, New York, 1988 (Box 22)
    Project # 88-647
  - Tompkins County Public Library, Ithaca, New York, 1989 (Box 22)
    Project # 89-642
  - Mental Health Services Building, Ithaca, New York, 1989 (Box 22)
    Project # 89-643
  - United Way of Tompkins County, Ithaca, New York, 1989 (Box 22)
    Project # 89-653
  - Tompkins County Courthouse Renovations, Ithaca, New York, 1990 (Box 22)
    Project # 90-657
  - Gifft Residence, Lansing, New York, 1990 (Box 22)
    Project # 90-660
  - Homer Avenue Methodist Church, Cortland, New York, 1991 (Box 22)
    Project # 91-666
  - Cooley Medical Building, Oneida, New York, 1992 (Box 22)
    Project # 92-528
  - Turcotte Residence, Ithaca, New York, 1992 (Box 22)
    Project # 92-672
  - Gardner Residence, Lansing, New York, 1992 (Box 22)
  - Elmira Community Residence, Elmira, New York, 1993 (Box 22)
    Project # 93-681
  - Ironics' Roof, Ithaca, New York, 1994 (Box 22)
    Project # 94-686
  - Drop-In Children's Center, Ithaca, New York, 1994 (Box 22)
  - Lakeside Nursing Home, Ithaca, New York, 1994 (Box 22)
    Project # 94-696
  - Tompkins County Public Library, Ithaca, New York, 1995 (Box 22)
    Project # 95-698
  - Old Hundred, Ithaca, New York, 1996 (Box 23)
    Project # 96-709
  - Vineyard Residence, Ithaca, New York, 1996 (Box 23)
    Project # 96-717
  - Malott Hall Renovations, Cornell University, 1997 (Box 23)
    Project # 97-723
  - First Church of Christ, Scientist, Ithaca, New York, 1997 (Box 23)
    Project # 97-731
  - Day Hall Renovations, Cornell University, 1997 (Box 23)
    Project # 97-735
  - Hollister Hall Renovations, Cornell University, 1998 (Box 23)
    Project # 98-747
  - Cornell Golf Center, Cornell University, 1998 (Box 23)
    Project # 98-750
  - Ithaca City Hall Renovations, Ithaca, New York, 1998 (Box 23)
    Project # 98-762
  - Yvonne Grand Residence Addition, Erin, New York, 1999 (Box 23)
    Project # 99-768
  - Oneida Physicians Office Building, Oneida, New York, 1999 (Box 24)
    Project # 99-783
  - 160 Day Hall/HR Renovations, Cornell University, 2000 (Box 24)
    Project # 00-800
  - Cooley Professional Building, Site Plan, Oneida, New York, 2000 (Box 24)
  - Unitarian Church Annex, Ithaca, New York, 2001 (Box 24)
    Project # 01-801
  - Oneida OB/GYN Building, Oneida, New York (Box 24)
  - Oneida OB/GYN Building, Oneida, New York (Box 24)
  - Plant 2A Entry, Moog, Inc., East Aurora, New York (Box 24)
  - Monarch Machine Tool Co., Office Building & Factory, Cortlandsville, New York (Box 24)
  - Monarch Machine Tool Co., Office Addition, Cortlandsville, New York (Box 24)
  - Ithaca College Central Services Building, Ithaca, New York (Box 24)
  - Moog Inc., Office & Plant, East Aurora, New York - Harris Armstrong, Architect, 1966 (Box 24)
  - Utica City Hall - Furniture, Utica, New York, 1966 (Box 24)
  - CCBI Apartment Office Building, Syracuse, New York, 1967 (Box 24)
  - McGraw House, Ithaca, New York - Anton J. Egner & Associates, Architects, 1968 (Box 24)
    Project # 6842
  - Project Unknown (Box 24)
  - Schoolhouse Manor, 1980 (Box 30)
  - South Hill School, Ithaca, New York (Box 33)
  - Belle Sherman School, Ithaca, New York (Box 33)
  - East Hill School, Ithaca, New York (Box 33)
  - Tompkins County Trust Company - Drive In Bank, 1961 (Box 34)
  - Poultry Building, Cornell University, Ithaca, New York, 1965 (Box 34)
  - Tompkins County Memorial Hospital - aka Biggs Memorial Hospital (Box 36)
  - Newark Valley School District Temporary School Building, 1966 (Box 36)
  - Alpha Phi Sorority, Ithaca, New York - Holt, Architect (Box 101)
  - Alpha Delta Phi Fraternity (Box 101)
  - Phi Gamma Delta Fraternity (Box 101)
  - Central Fire Station, Ithaca, New York (Box 101)
  - Seneca Lake State Park Bathhouse (Box 102)
  - Finger Lakes State Park Administration Building, 1969 (Box 102)
  - Gardner Road Elementary and Big Flats Elementary, Horseheads, New York (Box 102)
  - The Hickories, Owego, New York, 1969 (Box 102)
    Project # 440
  - Auer Residence (Box 102)
  - Ithaca Savings and Loan Association, Ithaca, New York (Box 102)
  - Clynes Residence (Box 102)
    Project # 369
  - Geer Apartment Addition to Laboratory, Cayuga Heights, New York (Box 102)
  - Clute Memorial Park Roller Skating Rink, Watkins Glen, New York (Box 102)
    Project # 406
  - Monarch Machine Tool Company Overhead Crane System and Operating Spray Paint Booth, Cortlandsville, New York (Box 102)
    Project # 403
  - Reconstruction Home, Ithaca, New York (Box 102)
    Project # 273
  - Beta Sigma Rho Fraternity (Box 102)
    Project # 313
  - Finger Lakes Auto Club (Box 102)
    Project # 319
  - Chenango Valley State Park Bathhouse and Concession, 1966 (Box 102)
  - Ithaca Senior High School, Ithaca, New York - Perkins & Will, Architects (Box 102)
  - Long Point Boat Launching Site (Box 103)
  - Lodi Point Boat Launching Site (Box 103)
  - Sampson State Park Golf House (Box 103)
  - Sampson State Park Water Supply Intake & Water Main Connection, 1961 (Box 103)
  - Sampson State Park Campsite - Comfort Station & Bathhouse, 1965 (Box 103)
  - Sampson State Park Shelter Building (Box 103)
  - Taughannock Falls State Park Comfort Station, 1966 (Box 103)
  - Glen National Bank, Watkins Glen, New York (Box 103)
  - Dryden Methodist Church, Dryden, New York (Box 103)
  - Andes Swimming Pool, Andes, New York (Box 103)
  - Roy H. Park Swimming Pool (Box 103)
  - Tuning Fork Square, 1969 (Box 103)
    Project # 437
  - Danby Fire Station, Danby, New York (Box 103)
  - Danby Elementary School, Danby, New York (Box 103)
  - Marathon Central School Bus Garage, Marathon, New York (Box 103)
  - Tioga Schools, Tioga County, New York, 1961 (Box 103)
  - Tioga Elementary School (Box 103)
    Project # 362
  - Tioga Elementary School Alterations, 1970 (Box 103)
  - Tioga Middle School, 1970 (Box 103)
  - Tioga High School, 1970 (Box 103)
    Project # 445
  - Tioga Bus Garage (Box 103)
    Project # 294
  - Big Flats School and Ridge Road School, Horseheads, New York - Carl W. Clark, Architect (Box 104)
  - Broad Street Elementary School - Haskell, Considine & Haskell, Architects, 1957 (Box 104)
    Project # 1873
  - Big Flats School, Horseheads, New York - Considine & Haskell, Architects, 1960 (Box 104)
    Project # 2014
  - Enfield Elementary School, Enfield, New York - Richard E. Metzger, Architect (Box 104)
  - Elementary School, Town of Carolina, New York- Tallman & Tallman, Architects (Box 104)
  - U.S. Post Office - G.S.A., Ithaca, New York, 1964 (Box 104)
  - Hotel Phoenicia Intercontinental, Beirut, Lebanon - Edward D. Stone, Architect, 1957 (Box 104)
    Project # 551-2
  - U.S. Embassy, New Delhi, India - Edward D. Stone, Architect (Box 104)
  - Heinz Research Center Building - Skidmore, Owings & Merrill, Architects, 1957 (Box 104)
  - Seymour Kimmel Residence, Mamaroneck, New York - Edward D. Stone, Architect (Box 104)
  - Tompkins County Memorial Hospital, Ithaca, New York - Eggers & Higgins, Architects, 1953 (Box 104)
    Project # 656
  - Division 15A (Box 104)
  - Warren W. Clute Memorial Park Roller Skating Rink, Watkins Glen, New York (Box 104)
  - St. Paul's Church (Box 104)
  - Stagg Residence East Terrace (Box 104)
  - Dean Residence, Ithaca, New York (Box 104)
  - Curtiss Residence, Ithaca, New York (Box 104)
- Series IV. Photographic Materials
  - Hollister Hall Construction, Cornell University, Ithaca, New York (Box 25)
  - Hollister Hall, Cornell University, Ithaca, New York (Box 25)
  - Visitor Center, Balch & Noyes Hall, Cornell University, Ithaca, New York, 1999 (Box 25)
    Project # 99-779
  - Monarch, Cortland, New York (Box 25)
  - 411 N. Tioga, Ithaca, New York, 1996 (Box 25)
  - Halkiopoulos, 1997 (Box 25)
    Project # 97-740
  - Newlin Residence, Brooktondale, New York, 1996 (Box 25)
    Project # 96-715
  - J. Michael's Restaurant, Ithaca, New York, 1996 (Box 25)
    Project # 96-718
  - East Hill School Condo, Ithaca, New York, 1997 (Box 25)
    Project # 97-724
  - Sevanna Park Balconies, 1997 (Box 25)
    Project # 97-726
  - Freeville Community Residence, 1994 (Box 25)
  - First Church of Christ, Scientist, 1997 (Box 25)
  - Montour Falls House (Box 25)
  - Ithaca Youth Bureau, Architectural Record, Ithaca, New York, 1998 (Box 25)
  - Ramada Tower, slides, Ithaca, New York (Box 25)
  - Misc. Unidentified, Greenpoint (Box 25)
  - Old Courthouse, Ithaca, New York, 1975 (Box 25)
  - Unidentified Bathhouse, Swimming Pool, 1967 (Box 25)
  - Aruba, 1973-1974 (Box 25)
  - Tompkins County Houses, 1983 (Box 25)
  - Watkins Glen (Box 25)
  - Watkins Glen State Park Camping, slides (Box 25)
  - Cayuga Lake Mud Lock (Box 25)
  - Whitney Point Reservoir Upper Lisle (Box 25)
  - Whitney Point Reservoir South Site (Box 25)
  - Otisco Lake (Box 25)
  - Baldwinsville (Box 25)
  - Shepard Niles (Box 25)
  - Barcelona Harbor, slides (Box 25)
  - Delaware County Park (Box 25)
  - Corning (Box 25)
  - Andes Pool (Box 25)
  - Irondequiot Harbor (Box 25)
  - Negatives rolls, project names identified in many cases (Box 26)
  - Unidentified images (Box 26)
  - Hollister Hall, Cornell University, Ithaca, New York (Box 27)
  - Unidentified residence (Box 27)
  - Freeville Community Residence, 1994 (Box 27)
  - J.N. Adam Day Treatment Facility, 1986 (Box 27)
  - Unidentified suburban commercial building, aerial view (Box 27)
  - Unidentified photographs, includes Cornell University campus buildings (Box 101)
  - Photo Negatives Misc.: Central Tech (Syracuse, NY), November 1, 1975 (Box 101)
  - Photo Negatives Misc.:Park Square (Rochestor, NY), January 1, 1976 (Box 101)
  - Photo Negatives Misc.:Moog (East Aurora, NY), May 5, 1976 (Box 101)
  - Photo Negatives Misc.: Unidentified (Box 101)
  - Photo Album: Unidentified School (Box 101)
  - Photo Album: Moog (Box 101)
  - Photo Album: Aruba (Box 101)
- Series V. Drawings
  - Chronology of Architects & Architectural Firms in Ithaca, New York, 1883-1989 - W.H. Miller to Downing, 484
  - Marketing DBM, Poster, 484
  - Scorpian Frat House - Gibb, Architect, July 1 ,1927; 1
    Project # 29(?)
  - Eagles, 1928; 2
  - Ithaca Gun Woodshop, Ithaca, New York, 1927; 3
  - Elmira Heights Grade School, Elmira Heights, New York - Pierce & Bickford, Architects, 1929; 4
  - Gussie Gaskel Residence - Sherwood Holt, Architect, 1939; 5
  - Delta Gamma #50 - Holt, Architect, 1941; 6
  - Kappa Alpha - Holt, Architect, 1955; 6
  - Pi Beta Phi Sorority - Holt, Architect, 1955; 6
    Project # 257
  - Central Fire Station - Holt, Architect, 7
  - Elementary School - Jeanne Downing, 8
  - West Hill School, Ithaca, New York, 1949; 9
    Project # 49 - 192
  - Ithaca Gun Boiler House, Ithaca, New York, 1949; 10
    Project # 49 - 194
  - Cushman Apartment Building, Charlottesville, Virginia, 1949; 11
  - Keller Residence, Early 1950s; 12
  - Miscellaneous Residences, Early 1950s; 13
  - Marshall Residence, Charlottesville, Virginia, 1950; 14
    Project # 113
  - Bill Downing Residence, Charlottesville, Virginia, 1950; 15
    Project # 116 - R
  - Guy Davis Residence, Centenary, South Carolina, 1951; 16
    Project # 117
  - Samuel Ruday, Charlottesville, Virginia, 1951; 17
    Project # 119
  - Nulson Residence, Charlottesville, Virginia, 1951; 18
    Project # 120
  - Ithaca Gun Addition, Ithaca, New York, 19
  - Residence #138, 1952; 20
    Project # 138
  - Residence #142, 1952; 20
    Project # 142
  - Greek Orthodox Church, Charlottesville, Virginia, 1953; 21
    Project # 53-143
  - Labonte Residence - Holt, Architect, 1939; 22
  - Club Café - Baker, Heyward, Llorens?, Architects, 1947; 22
  - Tourist Court for Samuel Baxendale, Charlottesville, Virginia, 22
  - Apartment Building for James Stratos, Charlottesville, Virginia, 1954; 22
  - General Plan "Crestmont", Charlottesville, Virginia - Architect unknown, Engineer B. Aubrey Huffman, 1955; 22
  - Garden House for Jeanne Downing, 2003; 22
    Project # 2003
  - JNA Existing Building Profile, 22
  - Miscellaneous Unidentified Renderings, Plans, etc., 22
  - Charlottesville Christian Church at Cherry Avenue, Charlottesville, Virginia, October 16, 1953; 23
    Project # 146
  - Community Chest Building Alterations, May 6, 1905; 24
    Project # 235
  - Hart Residence, Shadyside, Ohio, 1954; 25
    Project # 162
  - Kappa Delta, 1955; 26
    Project # 232
  - Pi Beta Phi, 1955; 26
  - Phi Epsilon Pi, 1955; 26
    Project # 258
  - South Hill School, 1955; 27
    Project # 55-241
  - Moog, 27
  - J.N. Adam Day Treatment Facility, 27
  - Alpha Phi, 1956; 28
  - Residences at the Riverdale, 1956; 29
  - TC Memorial Hospital, 1957; 30
    Project # 57-265
  - TC Memorial Hospital, Building M Animal House, 1957; 31
    Project # ? (57-265 crossed out)
  - Acacia, 1959; 32
    Project # 277
  - Acacia, 1959; 33
  - Kappa Kappa Gamma, 1959; 34
    Project # 272, A - 13, 14
  - Beta Sigma Rho, Preliminaries, 1960; 35
    Project # 313, C-24
  - 519 Cayuga Heights Rd, Ithaca, New York, 36
  - Jirka Residence, 37
  - Corcoran Properties, 38